Guide to the Claire Kincannon theatre collection, 1955-2011
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Washington, D.C., 1971-2011; (24 boxes)
  - The Miser, The Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, April 8, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Helen Hayes Awards, National Theatre, April 28, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Stuttgart Ballet, Kennedy Center, May, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Stagebill; Press Release; Media Kit.
  - Ghetto, Kennedy Center, May, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Production of the Haifa Municipal Theatre of Israel. Stagebill.
  - Herman Wouk's The Caine Mutiny Court-Martial, Kennedy Center, May, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Twelfth Night, The Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, May, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Macbeth, Source Theatre Company, May, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Old Times, Arena Stage, May 9, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Ma Rainey's Black Bottom, Studio Theatre, May 14, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Program; Press Release.
  - Biloxi Blues, National Theatre, June, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Tickets; Stagebill; Press Release.
  - 1984, Kennedy Center, July, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Shout Up A Morning, Kennedy Center, July, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Production of the La Jolla Playhouse. Stagebill; Photograph.
  - Beehive, Arena Stage, July 14, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Legends!, National Theatre, August, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Theatre School Schedule of Classes, Round House Theatre, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Schedule.
  - Vienna: Lusthaus, Kennedy Center, September, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Romeo and Juliet, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, September, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Press Release; Newspaper Articles; Publicity Packet; Program.
  - Juggle and Hyde, Arena Stage, September 2, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Program; Magazine; Newspaper Article.
  - Slab Boys Trilogy, Studio Theatre, September 17, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Program; Press Release; Studio Theatre Newspaper.
  - The Water Engine, Round House Theatre, September 25, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Press Release; Program; Mailer.
  - Broadway Bound, National Theatre, October, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Tickets; Press Release; Stagebill.
  - The Marriage of Bette and Boo, Arena Stage, October 3, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Chinese Golden Dragon Acrobats and Magicians of Taipei, Ford's Theatre, November, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - A Raisin in the Sun, Kennedy Center, November, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Goya, Washington Opera, November 10, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - American Dreams, Round House Theatre, November 19, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - The Perfect Party, Kennedy Center, December, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Les Miserables, Kennedy Center, December, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    Souvenir Brochure; Stagebill.
  - The Piggy Bank, Arena Stage, December 5, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Program; Press Release; American's Arena Publication.
  - Arsenic and Old Lace, Kennedy Center, January, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Stagebill; Press Release; Newspaper Article.
  - Crime and Punishment, Arena Stage, January 2, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Program; Newspaper Article; America's Arena Publication.
  - Glengarry Glen Ross, Arena Stage, January 30, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Program; Newspaper Article; Press Release.
  - The Mikado, Kennedy Center, February, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - All My Sons, Ford's Theatre, February 7, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Mandragola, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, February 17, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Photograph; Press Release; Mailer; Program.
  - The Winter's Tale, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, February 17, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Invitation; Program; Press Release.
  - The Entertainer, Studio Theatre, March 11, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - The Nest, Round House Theatre, March 12, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Program; Press Release; Newspaper Article.
  - Ourselves Alone, Arena Stage, March 20, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - American College Theatre Festival XIX, Kennedy Center, March 30, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - I'm Not Rappaport, National Theatre, April, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Photograph; Press Release; Media Kit, Stagebill.
  - Love's Labor's Lost, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, April, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Press Release; Invitation.
  - Heartbreak House, Arena Stage, April 13, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Helen Hayes Awards, Kennedy Center, May 4, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Invitation; Press Releases; Program.
  - As Is, Studio Theatre, May 13, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Spoleto Festival, Charleston, S.C., May, June, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    Media Package
  - The Crucible, Arena Stage, June 6, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Invitation; Program; Photograph
  - Sherlock's Last Case, Kennedy Center, July, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cats, National Theatre, July, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Press Release; Stagebill.
  - The Immigrant: A Hamilton County Album, Arena Stage, July 7, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Ticket stub; Invitation; Program; Press Release; Newspaper Article.
  - Chili Queen, Kennedy Center, July 15, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Satchmo, Kennedy Center, August, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Sweet Charity, National Theatre, September, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Quilters, Castle Art Center, September, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Press Release; Two Photographs
  - I Never Sang for My Father, Kennedy Center, September 2, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Cabaret, Kennedy Center, September 9, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - The Witch of Edmonton, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, September 29, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Invitation; Program; Press Release; Newspaper Article.
  - All the King's Men, Arena Stage, October, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - North Shore Fish, Studio Theatre, October, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Joe Turner's Come and Gone, Arena Stage, October 2, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - American Indian Dance Theatre, Ford's Theatre, November, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Lady, Be Good!, Kennedy Center, November, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - HMS Pinafore, Kennedy Center, December, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - All's Well That Ends Well, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, December, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Newspaper Article; Program; Ticket Stubs; Mailer.
  - Light Up the Sky, Arena Stage, December 11, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Invitation; Program; Ticket Stubs; Press Release.
  - Actors Theatre of Louisville, KY, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Ten photographs.
  - Enrico VI, Arena Stage, January 1, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - The Colored Museum; Split Second, Studio Theatre, January 20, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Macbeth, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, February, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Photograph; Press Release; Program.
  - Les Blancs, Arena Stage, February 5, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - The Night Hank Williams Died, New Playwrights Theatre, February 5, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Invitation; Program; Photograph; Magazine Article.
  - M. Butterfly, National Theatre, February 10, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Stagebill; Press Release; Photograph.
  - The Search for Signs of Intelligent Life in the Universe, Kennedy Center, March, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Ah, Wilderness!, Studio Theatre, March 16, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Program; Press Release; Photograph.
  - The Cocoanuts, Arena Stage, April, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Drood!, Kennedy Center, April, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Cats, National Theatre, April, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - The Merchant of Venice, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, May 4, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Magazine Article; Tickets; Program; Photograph; Press Release.
  - The Cherry Orchard, Arena Stage, May 6, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Helen Hayes Awards, National Theatre, May 9, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Press Releases.
  - On the Verge, Round House Theatre, May 19, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Spoleto Festival, Charleston, S.C., May 20 - June 5, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    Invitation.
  - Les Miserables, Kennedy Center, July, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Press Kit; Stagebill.
  - Ain't Misbehavin', National Theatre, July, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Press Release; Stagebill; Photograph.
  - Words and Music, Ford's Theatre, September, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Sullivan and Gilbert, Kennedy Center, September, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Hunting Cockroaches, Studio Theatre, September, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Baby with the Bathwater, Round House Theatre, September 8, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Antony and Cleopatra, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, September 20, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Media Kit; Program.
  - Born Yesterday, National Theatre, October, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Ring Around the Moon, Arena Stage, October 14, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Anything Goes, National Theatre, November, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Richard II, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, November, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - The Gifts of the Magi, Studio Theatre, November, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Me and My Girl, Lyric Opera House, Baltimore, December, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Photograph; Letter.
  - Playboy of the West Indies, Arena Stage, December 2, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - A Chorus of Disapproval, Arena Stage, December 30, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Program; Photographs.
  - 12th-14th Humana Festival, Classics in Context, Actor's Theatre of Louisville, KY, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    Program; Playbills
    Moscow Art Theatre: Past, Present, Future publication
  - Lady Day at Emerson's Bar and Grill, Studio Theatre, January 4, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Steel Magnolias, Kennedy Center, February, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Michael Feinstein in Concert, Ford's Theatre, March 1, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Press Kit; Program.
  - 13th Annual Humana Festival of New American Plays, Actor's Theatre of Louisville, March 1 - April 8, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - A Lie of the Mind, Arena Stage, March 3, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Nothing Sacred, Arena Stage, March 25, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - On the Town, Arena Stage, April 21, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - King of Hearts, Kennedy Center, May, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Photographs; Stagebill; Program; Tickets.
  - Speed-the-Plow, Kennedy Center, May, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Photographs; Stagebill.
  - The World According to Me!, Kennedy Center, June, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Into the Woods, Kennedy Center, June, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Tickets; Stagebill; Photographs.
  - Penn and Teller, National Theatre, June, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Incommunicado, Kennedy Center, July, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Photograph; Press Release; Stagebill.
  - Road to Mecca, Kennedy Center, July, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Photograph; Stagebill; Press Release.
  - Gypsy, Kennedy Center, August, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 3 Penny Opera, National Theatre, September, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - A Midsummer Night's Dream, Arena Stage, September 22, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    Program; Photograph; Press Release.
  - The Glass Menagerie, Arena Stage, October 6, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Press Release; Photograph; Program.
  - Kaufmania, Arena Stage, November, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Red Army Song and Dance Ensemble, Kennedy Center, November, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Invitation; Press Release; Newspaper Articles.
  - The Piano Lesson, Kennedy Center, November, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Photograph; Stagebill.
  - The Man Who Came to Dinner, Arena Stage, November 16, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    Invitation; Program; Photograph; Press Release.
  - A Tuna Christmas, Kennedy Center, December, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Monteith and Rand, Arena Stage, December 12, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Stand Up Tragedy, Arena Stage, January 12, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Invitation; Program; Media Kit.
  - Emerald City, Round House Theatre, January 25, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Merrily We Roll Along, Arena Stage, January 30, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Stardust, Kennedy Center, February, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Program, Photographs.
  - A Doll House, Arena Stage, March 2, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Made In Bangkok, Studio Theatre, March 14, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Program; Media Kit.
  - Sarafina!, Kennedy Center, April, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Fences, Arena Stage, April 20, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Invitation; Photograph; Program; Press Release.
  - Juno and the Paycock, Arena Stage, May 4, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Starlight Express, Kennedy Center, June, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Les Miserables, National Theatre, July, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - The Bolshoi Ballet, Wolf Trap, July, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Arena Stage 40th Anniversary, 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Shogun, Kennedy Center, September, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - The Abbey, Kennedy Center, September, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Closer Than Ever, Arena Stage, September 4, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Invitation; Program; Newspaper Article; Photograph.
  - The Caucasian Chalk Circle, Arena Stage, September 21, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - The Playboy of the Western World, Kennedy Center, September 10, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Cerceau, Arena Stage, October 12, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Othello, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, November, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Our Town, Arena Stage, November 15, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - From the Mississippi Delta, Arena Stage, December, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - A Tuna Christmas, Kennedy Center, December, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Grand Hotel, Kennedy Center, December, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Lost in Yonkers, National Theatre, January, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Stagebill; Press release; Notes.
  - Lucifer's Child, Kennedy Center, February, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Fuente Ovejune, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, February, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Program; Photograph; Newspaper Articles; Magazine; Press Release.
  - Pygmalion, Arena Stage, February, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 15th Annual Humana Festival of New American Plays, Actors Theatre of Louisville, March, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - The Heidi Chronicles, Kennedy Center, March, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - One Monkey Don't Stop No Show, National Theatre, March, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Stagebill; Media Kit; Newspaper Articles.
  - She Stoops to Conquer, Arena Stage, March 20, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Vivisections from the Blown Mind, Arena Stage, April, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    News release; Photograph; Program.
  - King Lear, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, April 23, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Press release; Newsletter; Program.
  - The Two Gentlemen of Verona, Arena Stage, May 3, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Invitation; Program; News Release.
  - Helen Hayes Awards, National Theater, May 6, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    News Release; Invitation; Program.
  - The Seagull, Arena Stage, May 22, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Press Release; Program; Invitation; Newspaper Article.
  - Phantom of the Opera, Kennedy Center, June, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - The Boys Next Door, Wayside Theatre, Middletown,VA, June, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - The Lion in Winter, Wayside Theatre, July, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Mlada, Filene Center Lines, Wolf Trap Farm Park, July 14-15, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Production of the Bolshoi Opera. Program; Photograph.
  - White Oak Dance Project, Filene Center lines, Wolf Trap Farm Park, July 30, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Tru, Kennedy Center, September, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - How the Other Half Loves, Wayside Theatre, Middletown, VA, September, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Coriolanus, Shakespeare Theatre at the Folger, September 10, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Program; Press Release; Newsletter.
  - The Berliner Ensemble, Actors Theatre of Louisville, October, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Three Photographs.
  - Tales from the Vienna Woods, Actors Theatre of Louisville, October, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    Playbill; Two Photographs.
  - Yerma, Arena Stage, October 4, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - The Women, Studio Theatre, October 23, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - On Borrowed Time, Arena Stage, November, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    Press Release; Postcard.
  - Two Trains Running, Kennedy Center, November, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Introduction of Lansburgh Theatre, Shakespeare Theatre, November 7, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    Press Kit.
  - Nobody Here But Us Chickens, Studio Theatre, November 14, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - A Wonderful Life, Arena Stage, November 15, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Saint Joan, Shakespeare Theatre, November 26, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Bye Bye Birdie, Kennedy Center, December, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    Stagebill; Press Kit.
  - Jar the Floor, Arena Stage, December 7, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    Program; Press Kit.
  - The Nutcracker, Loudon Ballet Company, December 7, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Other Peoples Money, Wayside Theatre, ca. 1992 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Private Lives, National Theatre, January, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - The American Plan, Studio Theatre, January 8, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - African Tourist, Woolly Mammoth Theatre Company, January 13, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - The Father, and The Stronger, Arena Stage, February 7, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - The School For Wives, Arena Stage, February 14, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Invitation; Program; Press Release; Photograph.
  - 16th Annual Humana Festival of New American Plays, Actors Theatre of Louisville, February 18-March 28, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    Program; Guest list.
  - Much Ado About Nothing, Shakespeare Theatre, February 25, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Program; Press Kit; Two photographs.
  - A Chorus Line, National Theatre, March, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Measure for Measure, Shakespeare Theatre, March, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - The Wizard of Hip, Studio Theatre, March, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Solitary Confinement, Kennedy Center, March 7, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Stagebill; Press Kit; Photograph.
  - Conrack, Ford's Theatre, March 9, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Pump Boys and Dinettes, Kennedy Center, March 12, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Program; Press Release; Key chain.
  - Mrs. Klein, Arena Stage, April, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - The Helen Hayes Awards, National Theatre, April 27, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Berlin Cabaret, Kennedy Center, April 30, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Production of the Theater des Westens. Stagebill; Press Kit.
  - Buddy: The Buddy Holly Story, Kennedy Center, May, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Lettuce and Lovage, National Theatre, May, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Falsettoland, Studio Theatre, May, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Prelude to a Kiss, Olney Theatre, May 5, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - The Visit, Arena Stage, May 8, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Kvetch, Woolly Mammoth Theatre Company, June 15, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Valentine Fairy Tales, Very Special Arts Virginia - Loudoun County, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Play On, Arena Stage, November 3, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Contemporary American Theatre Festival, Shepherdstown, WV, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Washington DC and Northern Virginia playbills, 2001-2011 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Loudoun Symphony 10th anniversary concert
    Waterford concert series: The Back Sinfonia
    Waterford concert series: Musical Remarks
    Capitol Steps: Who put the mock in democracy? It's the Capital Steps
    Oklahoma!, Arena Stage
    August Wilson's Gem of the Ocean, Arena Stage
    She Loves Me, Arena Stage
  - Washington DC playbills, 2002-2005 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    A Tribute to Sergei Prokofiev, Kennedy Center
    Ain't Misbehavin', Arena Stage
    An Evening at the Oscars, Loudoun Symphony, Middleburg, VA
    Anna Christie, Arena Stage
    The Best Man, Radio Theatre Live!
    Chicago, Knoxville Civic Auditorium, TN
    Choral Arts Society of Washington, Kennedy Center
    Diana Krall, Kennedy Center
    Eudora Welty Remembered, Folger Shakespeare Library
    Hallelujah, Baby!, Arena Stage
    Love's Labour's Lost, Catholic University of America
    Mostly Sondheim, Kennedy Center
    Pacific Overtures, Kennedy Center
    Passion, Kennedy Center
    PEN/Faulkner awards for fiction, Folger Shakespeare Library
    The Play About the Baby, The Studio Theatre
    Roberta Flack, Music Center at Strathmore
    Runaway Home, The Studio Theatre
    The Shape of Things, The Studio Theatre
  - National Press Club, Silver Owls, 2004-2008 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Fourth Estate Award Dinner honoring Christiane Amanpour
    The Order of the Owl, Initiating Art Buchwald
    The Order of the Owl, Initiating Austing H. Kiplinger and Donald A. Ritchie
    The Order of the Owl, Initiating Mark Russell
    Spring Hoot: A Grand Old Club Salutes A Grand Old Hotel
    The Order of the Owl, Initiating John Eaton
  - The Kennedy Center, playbills, 2004-2011 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Kennedy Center News (September-October 2004 and May-August 2004)
    Five by Tenn (ticket, press packet)
    The Light in the Piazza
    Salome
    Madama Butterfly
    Marian McPartland's 89th Birthday Celebration on Marian McPartland's Piano Jazz
    Washington National Opera's Iphigenie en Tauride
    Washington National Opera's Macbeth
  - The Kennedy Center, playbills, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    A View from the Bridge, Washington National Opera
    Madame Butterfly, Washington National Opera
    National Symphony Orchestra
    Sophie's Choice, Washington National Opera
  - Washington DC playbills, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    Cabaret, Arena Stage
    Connecting Lines: New Poetry from Mexico, The Cultural Institute of Mexico
    The Evening Parade, Marine Barracks Washington
    Fiddler on the Roof, Olney Theatre Center, MD
    Hansel and Gretel, The Lincoln Theatre
    Ibis, Waterford, VA
    Opera in Waterford, Domingo-Cafritz Young Artists, Waterford, VA
    The Persians, Shakespeare Theatre Company
    Waterford Home Tours and Crafts Exhibit, Waterford, VA
  - National Symphony Orchestra, Kennedy Center, January, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - The Heidi Chronicles, Arena Stage, April 6, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Washington National Opera, Kennedy Center, September, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Playbill.
  - Barbara Cook's Spotlight, Kennedy Center, October, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Washington DC playbills and magazines, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Applause at Strathmore
    The Arthur Miller Festival: Death of a Salesman, A View from the Bridge, Arena Stage
    Blues Alley Jazz Supper Club
    Cymbeline, Round House Silver Spring
    Kennedy Center News
    La Traviata, Washington National Opera, Kennedy Center
    Musical Remarks, John Wesley Church, Waterford, VA
    The Pearl Fishers, Washington National Opera, Kennedy Center
    The Price, Theatre J
    Strathmore News
  - Wishful Thinking, Arena Stage, September, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Rabbit Hole, Olney Theatre, September, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Pearl Fishers, Kennedy Center, October, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Production of the Washington National Opera. Playbill.
  - Washington DC playbills, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Antony and Cleopatra, Lansburgh Theatre
    Ariadne auf Naxos, Washington National Opera, Kennedy Center
    Chicago, National Theatre
    Falstaff, Washington National Opera, Kennedy Center
    I Love a Piano, Arena Stage
    Master Singers of Virginia, Waterford, VA
    Peter Grimes, Washington National Opera, Kennedy Center
    Turandot, Washington National Opera, Kennedy Center
  - Strathmore News Magazine, March-May 2009-2010 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Washington DC playbills, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    The Marriage of Figaro, Washington National Opera, Kennedy Center
    Porgy and Bess, Washington National Opera, Kennedy Center
    Reasons to be Pretty, The Studio Theatre
  - Headshots (Box 28, Folder 1)